unroll.me 2019-12-16

# Privacy Policy - Unroll.Me

Last updated on September 16, 2019

Data security and privacy are a priority for Unroll.me, a wholly-owned subsidiary of Slice Technologies, Inc. and its group companies (“Unroll.me” or “we”). This privacy policy describes:

  * the information we collect through our websites, apps and other consumer-facing services (the “Service”);
  * how we use this information;
  * with whom we share it;
  * and how we protect it.

This privacy policy also provides you with information about:

  * how you can request to access, stop the collection of, or delete your personal information (information that can be used to locate or identify you);
  * how to withdraw any consent you previously provided to us; and
  * where to go if you have questions about our privacy practices.

## Information that we collect and how we use it

We collect information from you in several ways:

  * you directly provide us with some information
  * you authorize us to collect other types of information, and
  * we automatically collect certain types of information.

Information you provide to us: When you register for the Service, you provide us with basic contact information, such as name and email address. You may also provide us with information when you interact with us, such as:

  * when you sign up for email alerts
  * subscribe to receive information,
  * complete a survey, or
  * seek customer support.

From time to time we will request additional information from you so that we can provide you with a specific offer, function, or feature. We use the information that you provide us to:

  * bring you the Service,
  * allow you to create and manage your account with us,
  * contact you about updates to and offers connected with the Service,
  * provide you with customer service and technical support, and
  * provide you with important notices about the Service.

Information you authorize us to collect: In order for us to perform tasks that are part of the Service, we need to access your email account(s). You authorize this access by agreeing to this privacy policy and providing any consent required by your email provider. provider.

We use this access to:

  * perform the functions of the Service, such as unsubscribing you from unwanted subscriptions and creating a “roll-up” of other subscriptions and/or transactions;
  * develop and offer new services; and
  * tailor content as part of our Service such as in our roll-up summaries

Additionally, unless otherwise restricted by your email provider, we use this access to support our e-commerce measurement business.

Measurement Products and Datasets: We access information from transaction-related emails that you receive to develop and prepare measurement products and datasets with the assistance of, and in combination with, data that is available to: our parent company, our affiliate companies, and other trusted business partners. Examples of the transaction-related emails that we or our trusted business partners process include purchase receipts, sales receipts, delivery confirmations and returns, subscription confirmations and cancellations, registration confirmations, transaction summaries and the like. The measurement information that we prepare is used by Fortune 500 companies, household name brands, investment companies, and other businesses for purposes such as:

  * understanding industry and business trends;
  * improving the goods, services or offers provided to customers;
  * improving business operations;
  * understanding the competitive landscape;
  * understanding where to make investments; or
  * gaining other business insights.

As described in the section “How We Protect Your Information,” unless otherwise restricted by your email service provider, after we collect your information:

  * we undertake a process that is designed to de-identify this information,
  * we may further combine or aggregate this information with other information available to us or our trusted business partners; and once the information is processed,
  * we use this processed information for measurement purposes, and
  * we share this processed information with trusted business partners for their analytics and other business purposes, subject to applicable laws.

Information that we automatically collect. We may automatically collect information about the way that you use or interact with our Service so that we can:

  * tailor content within our Service, such as in roll-up summaries;
  * provide users with access to our website, app, service, or feature;
  * better understand our users, their interests and preferences; and
  * develop, deliver, and improve the services we offer.

The type of information we collect through automated means include technical details about the devices you use with our Service (such as IP address or other device identifier), usage information and statistics about your interaction with our websites, the URLs of our web pages that you visit, URLs of referring and exiting pages, page views, time spent on a page, number of clicks, platform type, and other information about how you use our Service.

Please note that if there are features of our Services that are provided by third parties, those parties also may use automated means of data collection that are subject to those third parties’ privacy notices and policies.

Here are some of the types of automated data collection that occur when you use our sites:

Web Browsers: When you visit one of our websites, your browser automatically sends us your internet protocol (“IP”) address so that the web pages you request can be sent to your computer or device. We use your IP address to determine additional information, such as whether the computer or device has ever been used to visit our site before, which site features were used most often, and how much time was spent on a page.

Cookies: We automatically collect information through “cookies,” which are text files placed on your device’s hard drive when you visit websites. Cookies can enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting a particular site. We use cookies to help us manage and understand how you use our website. For example, we use cookies for authentication purposes, to measure session activity on the site, and to determine which areas and features of the site are the most popular. If you wish to disable cookies, you can do so by adjusting the settings for the browser that you use. If you do choose to disable cookies through your browser, you will not be able to take full advantage of all our site features.

Web Beacons and Log Files: We may use “web beacons” (also known as internet tags, pixel tags, tracking pixels, and clear GIFs) on pages of our websites. These web beacons allow third parties to collect information such as the IP address of the device, the URL of the web page, the time the page was viewed, the type of browser used, and any additional information in cookies that may have been set by the third party. The information is typically collected in log files, which generally track traffic on our websites. We use web beacons to manage the content we present and for analytical purposes (such as understanding our users, and how they interact with our site, and assisting us in managing and improving our site and Service). We do not attempt to identify individual users through this information.

Do Not Track Browser Signals. At this time, our Service does not recognize automated browser signals regarding tracking mechanisms, which may include “do not track” instructions. However, you may be able to change your privacy preferences regarding the use of cookies and similar technologies through your browser, as described above.

## Information That We Share

We share the information we collect to our parent company and third party service providers, who help us with the processing and storage of your data and otherwise operate and improve our Service.

Additionally, unless otherwise restricted by your email provider, we share the information that we collect with:

  * our parent company, who helps us develop measurement products and datasets;
  * our affiliated companies, who enhance our measurement capabilities by combining the information that we collect with other information available to them;
  * third-party service providers that work with us to develop and resell measurement products; and
  * customers (including third parties and affiliates) that have access to our measurement products and datasets.

As described in the section “How We Protect Your Information,” unless otherwise restricted by your email service provider, after we collect your information:

  * we undertake a process that is designed to de-identify this information,
  * we may further combine or aggregate this information with other information available to us or our trusted business partners; and once the information is processed,
  * we use this processed information for measurement purposes, and
  * we share this processed information with trusted business partners for their analytics and other business purposes, subject to applicable laws.

We may also disclose information about you:

  * if we are required to do so by law or legal process,
  * to law enforcement authorities or other government officials,
  * when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity, or
  * if necessary to protect the vital interests of another individual.

Additionally, we reserve the right to transfer personal information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets.

## How We Protect Your Information

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect your personal information from accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use and other unlawful forms of processing. This said, no data transmissions through the internet or via mobile devices, or even the physical transfer of information, can be guaranteed to be completely secure. We cannot fully eliminate all security risks associated with personal information. As such, we do not ensure or warrant the security of any data or information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

Data security and privacy are a priority for us, and with the assistance of our parent company, our affiliated companies and other trusted business partners, unless otherwise restricted by your email service provider, after we collect your information:

  * we undertake a process that is designed to de-identify this information,
  * we may further combine or aggregate this information with other information available to us or our trusted business partners; and once the information is processed,
  * we use this processed information for measurement purposes, and
  * we share this processed information with trusted business partners for their analytics and other business purposes, subject to applicable laws.

## Restrictions

For users that signed into this Service through their Gmail account, Google restricts third parties from using its API tool to access Gmail account information("Your Google User Data"). This restriction will not apply to other Gmail users that sign up by providing us with an app password that was generated specifically as part of Google’s two-factor authentication process. To determine whether you are subject to this restriction, please go to the settings page of your Unroll.Me dashboard which can be accessed here

Additional Limits on Use of Your Google User Data: The following limits apply to information that we collect and process after June 1, 2019. Notwithstanding anything else in this Privacy Policy, if you provide the Service with access to the following types of Your Google User Data, the Service’s use of that data will be subject to these additional restrictions:

The Service will only use access to read, write, modify or control Gmail message bodies (including attachments), metadata, headers, and settings to provide you with the Service and will not transfer this Gmail data to others unless doing so is necessary to provide and improve these features, comply with applicable law, or as part of a merger, acquisition, or sale of assets. The Service will not use this Gmail data for serving advertisements. The Service will not allow humans to read this data unless we have your affirmative agreement for specific messages, doing so is necessary for security purposes such as investigating abuse, to comply with applicable law, or for the Service’s internal operations and even then only when the data have been aggregated and anonymized.

## Your Choices

In certain cases, you may have choices about how we use and disclose your personal information. For example, we will ask you before we use your personal information for any purpose incompatible with those purposes identified in this policy. If we provide you with any marketing messages, we also will give you an opportunity to opt out of receiving further messages.

You can also choose not to give us the information we request, as described in the “Information You Provide to Us” section of this policy. In some cases, if you decide not to provide information, we will not be able to provide you with access to the site you requested, or we may not be able to provide you with the service, feature or information you requested.

In some cases, you can stop or limit the information we collect by automated means. Please review the sections of this policy titled “Information Collected by Automated Means” to learn more about how you may be able to stop or limit our receipt of that information.

Should you wish to delete your account, you can do so by following these [instructions. ](https://support.unroll.me/hc/en-us/articles/200165526-How-do-I-delete-my-Unroll-Me-account-)You may also exercise and amend your choices by sending an email to us as specified in the “How to Contact Us” section below.

## Access and Correction

We will provide you with the ability to access and update certain information we have about you, such as the contact information you provide as part of your registration process. Please submit your request by sending an email to the address specified in the “How to Contact Us” section below. Please include your name, email address and postal address in your request so that we may respond appropriately.

## Links to Other Sites

We may provide links to other sites for your convenience and information. These sites may be operated by organizations not affiliated with Unroll.me, so we cannot control and are not responsible for their content, operation, or privacy practices. Those organizations may have their own privacy policies, which we strongly suggest you review if you use other sites. This Notice does not apply to those sites, even if we link to them or they link to us.

## Transfers of Information

As part of our international operations, we may transfer information about you to a jurisdiction where we do business. Even if those jurisdictions do not have the same privacy laws as the jurisdiction where you reside, we will treat your information as subject to the protections described in this policy.

Our service is currently not offered to individuals from the European Union, and we have discontinued service for individuals that may have signed up from the European Union.

## Updates to Our Privacy Notice

This privacy policy may be updated periodically to you to reflect changes in our information practices or relevant laws. We will indicate at the top of the policy when it was updated. Substantial changes to this policy will be effective 30 days after posting. Please review this Notice any time you access or use our sites to make sure you have reviewed the most recent version.

## How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments about this privacy policy or if you would like us to update information we have about you or your preferences, please contact us at [privacy@unroll.me](mailto:privacy@unroll.me).
